A Guide to the Records of Lieutenant Governor Lawrence Doulgas Wilder, 1975-1990 (bulk 1986-1989)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Files [Accession 33696], 1982-1989., Extent: 18.9 cu. ft. (54 boxes). (Box 20-73)
  - Subject files
    - F, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Falwell, Rev. Jerry, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Fixer, Freddie, Parade, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - G, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - G, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - G, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Garfield F. Childs Memorial Fund, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Gold Bowl, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Gold Bowl, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Gold Bowl, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Greater Washington Board of Trade, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Greater Richmond Informed Parents (GRIP), 1987 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - H, 1985 December-1986 June (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - H, 1986 July-December (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - H, 1987 January-March (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - H, 1987 April-May (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - H, 1987 June-December (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - H, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - H, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Henrico County, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Hilton Hotel, 1986-1988 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Home Builders Association, 1986-1988 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - I, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - I, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Infant mortality, 1986-1989 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - International Longshoremen's Association, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Iowa, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Israel trip, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - J, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - J, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - J, 1987-1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Jack and Jill of America, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Japan, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Japan, Trip to, 1986 July 20-28 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Japan, Trip to, 1986 July 20-28 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Jaycees (Richmond), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Jewish concerns, 1986-1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Jobs for Virginia graduates, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Jobs for Virginia graduates, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1989 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Judicial Conference on the 4th District, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - K, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - K, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - K, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - L, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - L, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - L, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Metro Richmond, 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - League of Women Voters, 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Letters, Birthday, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Letters, Commendation, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Letters, Condolence, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Literacy, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Luray Caverns, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Lynchburg Charter, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - M, 1986 January-June (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - M, 1986 July-December (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - M, 1987 January-May (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - M, 1987 June-December (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - M, 1988 January-June (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - M, 1988 July-December (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - M, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Maryland, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Maymont House (Richmond, Va.), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - MBC Cultural Arts Series, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Mc, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Medicaid, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Medi-Vac (Airplanes, helicopters), 1986 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Metro Richmond Chamber of Commerce, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Metro Richmond Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Military Retirees Club, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Museums, Va., Association of, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - N, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - N, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - N, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - National Conference of State Legislators, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey, 1985-1988 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk Navy Shipyard, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - N. Virginia Building Industry Association, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Nurses, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - O, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - O, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - O, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Old Dominion Medical Society, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Old Dominion Pharmaceutical Association, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Optimists, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - P, 1986 January-June (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - P, 1986 July-1987 January (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - P, 1987 January-March (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - P, 1987 April-June (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - P, 1987 July-December (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - P, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - P, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Pages (for Lt. Gov.), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Pages (for Gov.), 1986-188 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - People to People, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Peninsula Legal Aid Center, Inc., 1989 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Physicians, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Planning Council, The, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Poems, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Police, Va. State Association, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Poplar Forest (Forest, Bedford Co., Va.), 1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Population report, Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Ports, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Portsmouth (city), 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Prevent Blindness, National Society of, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Publications and books received, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Pulaski County, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - R, 1986 January-July (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - R, 1986 August-December (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - R, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - R, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - R, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Radio-TV stations, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Reading (Va.) Month, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Reynolds Metal Co., 1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Richmond Black Student Foundation, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Richmond City, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Richmond Newspapers, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Richmond Renaissance, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Richmond Rotary Club, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - River Foundation, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Roanoke Zoo Project, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Robinson, Roger W., Jr., 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Rosey Grier Youth Shelter (Richmond, Va.), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Rural Virginia Development Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - S, 1986 January-April (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - S, 1986 May-August (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - S, 1986 September-1987 January (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - S, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - S, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Save Our Cumberland County (S.O.C.C.O.), 1988 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Savings bonds, PSA, National, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Savings bonds, US, 1986-1988 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - St. Jude Children's Research Hospital, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - School Drop-Out Program, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - School projects, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - School projects, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 3-5)
    - School projects, 1989 January-February (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - School projects, 1989 March (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - School projects, 1989 April (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - School projects, 1989 May-August (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah Valley Travel Association, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Shipping, Commercial, 1982-1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Sickle cell anemia, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Silver-Haired Legislature, 1987 August 3-5 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Small Business Administration, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - South Carolina, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Southeast Virginia Economic Development, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Virginia Agriculture Association, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Spencer, Judge James Randolph, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - State Legislative Leaders Foundation, 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - State Legislatures, National Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Status of Blacks in the Commonwealth, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Snydor, Charles, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - T, 1986 January-June (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - T, 1986 July-December (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - T, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - T, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - T, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan trip, 1986 March (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Telegrams, 1986-1989 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Mary Helen, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Thornton, Frank J., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Tobacco Row, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Tracy, Dewvaul W., Jr., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, N. Virginia 2010 Plan, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Tuition Assistance grants, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - U, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - U, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - U, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Uniform state laws, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - United Way, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - University of Virginia, Institute of Government newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Urban League, 1986-1988 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Utopia Exchange, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - V, 1986 January-June (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - V, 1986 July-December (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - V, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - V, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Variable Annuity Marketing Co., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars (VFW), 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam Veterans, Virginia Council, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Association of Commonwealth Attorneys, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Association Community Action Agencies, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Association of Counties, 1986-1988 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Association of Drug and Alcohol Program, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Association of Life Underwriters, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Capitol Correspondents Association, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Center for World Trade, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Federation of Communities for Drug Free Youth, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Forum, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Girls State, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Magistrates Association, Inc., 1986 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Municipal League, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Network for Victims and Witnesses Conference, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Opera, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Power, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Press Association, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Retail Merchants Association, 1986-1988 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Review, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Sheriff's Association, 1986-1989 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - W, 1986 January-June (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - W, 1986 July-December (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - W, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - W, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - W, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Warner, Sen. John W., 1986 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Washington Association of Black Journalists, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Washington (D.C.), 1988 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Water resources, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Werner, James F., 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Who's Who in America, 1986-198/8 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Wikstrom, Nelson, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Willey Public Service Award, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Williamsburg Foundation, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - "Writing In My Life", 1986 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - X, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Y, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Y, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - YMCA, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Youth Suicide Prevention, 1985-1988 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Z, 1986-1988 (Box 73, Folder 18)